let quiz=[
    {
      question: "What state in the United States has the most nuclear power plants :",
      option: [
           "New York",
           "Illinois",
           "Pennsylvania",
           "South Carolina",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The U.S. population recieves the largest dose of ionizing radiation from :",
      option: [
           "Natural sources",
           "Fallout from nuclear weapons testing",
           "Nuclear medicine",
           "Nuclear power plants",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What substance was used as a moderator for the chain reaction in the first nuclear reactor :",
      option: [
           "Graphite",
           "Boron",
           "Water",
           "Cadmium",
      ],
       answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "The oklo reactor in Gabon, Africa, is significant because it :",
      option: [
           "was the first man-made reactor.",
           "was a natural fission reactor.",
           "was the first reactor used to generate electricity.",
           "produced the most electricity in a single year.",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Most of the nuclear power plants operating in the United States are :",
      option: [
           "pressurized water reactors",
           "boiling water reactors",
           "high-temperature gas-cooled reactors",
           "liquid-metal fast breeder reactors",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "As the December, 1990, which of the following countries generated the greatest percentage of its electricity by nuclear power :",
      option: [
           "England",
           "Japan",
           "United States",
           "France",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "An important safety feature required at U.S. nuclear power plants that was not present at the Chernobyl Power Plant in the Soviet Union was the :",
      option: [
           "reactor",
           "cooloing water",
           "control rods",
           "containment building",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "The National Council on Radiation Protection and Measurements estimates that the average exposure to ionizing radiation the individual Americans recieve annualy from ALL sources is about :",
      option: [
           "60 millirem",
           "100 millirem",
           "360 millirem",
           "500 millirem",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Spent fuel from a nuclear power plant cools down and loses most of its radioactivity through decay. In the first year, spent fuel loses about what percentage of its radioactivity :",
      option: [
           "10 percent",
           "50 percent",
           "80 percent",
           "100 percent",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "The Uranium fuel used worldwide is mainly in the form of :",
      option: [
           "U3O8",
           "UO2",
           "UF6",
           "U Metal",
      ],
      answer: 2 ,
    },
    {
  question: "Sea Water Freezes at :",
  option: [
  "the same temperature as fresh water",
  "At a Slightly high-temperature than fresh water",
  "At a Slightly low-temperature than fresh water",
  "Seawater does not freeze",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
{
  question: "In the United States, low Sulphur Coal can be found primarily in the :",
  option: [
  "northeast",
  "southeast",
  "midwest",
  "west",
  ],
  answer: 4, 
},
{
  question: "A cyclone is a engineering device that is used to :",
  option: [
  "Transport Materials",
  "Segregate Particles",
  "Control Switching devices",
  "Model fractals",
  ],
  answer: 2, 
},
{
  question: "Who is called the Father of Nuclear Navy ?",
  option: [
  "Edward Teller",
  "Robert Oppenheimer",
  "Hymen Rickover",
  "Chester Nimitz",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
{
  question: "If a metal can be drawn into wires relatively easily it is called :",
  option: [
  "Malleable",
  "Ductile",
  "Extractive",
  "Tactile",
  ],
  answer: 2, 
},
    ]   
